<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-01-05T20:25:36-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000//</id><title type="html">Atsuko Shimizu</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Portfolio Built!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/design/web/2017/01/05/portfolio-built.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Portfolio Built!" /><published>2017-01-05T18:37:00-05:00</published><updated>2017-01-05T18:37:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/design/web/2017/01/05/portfolio-built</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/design/web/2017/01/05/portfolio-built.html">&lt;p&gt;So after three years of procrastinating, I finally started building my own portfolio website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a good project to practice coding my design. I chose Jekyll because it was perfect for what I wanted: a blog and lightness. Their &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; is excellent and there’s a lot of resources on the web. (A designer whom I admire wrote &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@julesforrest/building-a-portfolio-with-jekyll-1883bce8e1a4#.e37bfp67a&quot;&gt;a Medium article&lt;/a&gt; about Jekyll, which also motivated me to learn!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used &lt;a href=&quot;http://getskeleton.com/&quot;&gt;Skeleton.css &lt;/a&gt; for the responsive framework, for the familiarity and simplicity of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve also learned a bit about Markdown, Sass, and syntax-highlighting along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another goal of this project was to practice writing design case studies. Visuals simply do not tell the thought process and decisions that went into a design. They don’t showcase that I can design with an intention. I hope to improve my writing skills by explaining my design processes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think this was a great way to start the new year! I’m a bit more motivated to fill this site with design and computer science adventures.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">So after three years of procrastinating, I finally started building my own portfolio website.</summary></entry></feed>
